sup everyone came was wanna see four
five here was a very special video today
now I know how much you all love my
dishes I make and upload every now and
my youtube channel and [ __ ] so I thought
hey cuz my fans love that and I give my
fans what they wanted because I'm cool
like that
I'll do another one so today [ __ ] we
are going to make you one of my all-time
favorite dishes the Sonic special Sonic
Underground breakfast or I like to call
it the ball bxr quickfix because that is
what the dish is based off of what you
will need for this is ranch dressing
which is grape jelly a piece of white
bread cuz you know what is right cheese
a block of girl oil milk and cheese it
is just completely optional but a blue
piece of candy this is to represent sock
the Hedgehog [ __ ] and then we got
raisins and a and some oatmeal I made
this I made this like it's it's a it's
blueberry oatmeal it's blueberry to
again represent sock cuz he's blue and
[ __ ] so what we will be doing is we will
be be making two two comp two components
two components for this meal there will
be a ball B component and a Sonic
component doesn't that sound [ __ ] you
bet it does [ __ ] now first off we will
start with a BBQ pond what we will do
again you also Unni enough we will take
the white bread we will cut it so that
it looks it is in the shape of Bobby's
head as you can see I have cut the crust
off of the bread next what we would do
is we would take a slice of American
cheese like this oh that's looking good
we we will set down the plate and put it
hold on [ __ ] this is some sticky
cheese now we will put it like that to
was up I said and as you can see it's
it's looking a bit like Bobby but it got
let you file so well we want to is we
want to put it on and measure it like
that and [ __ ] then we will want to bring
the edges in like that like yeah this is
my food network share all right here but
this isn't the food now look this is
teamily files YouTube page we get [ __ ]
done even when the impossible is
impossible [ __ ] now we flip it all
over so that it seemed a lot now after
that come to pump our [ __ ] we get you
assemble next what you would need to do
is we are going to take our ranch
dressing and put just a little dollop
right there on either side to look like
and then we are gonna take some raisins
check this a [ __ ] sad look at look at
look how cool this is you gonna take one
raisin one put it on like that you all
gonna take another raisin boom look at
that it's already looking like biology
up in this [ __ ] now now these are the
case optional but this is why I use it
every single [ __ ] time and if you
want to be a true su fan you need to do
the two you're going to take the wrapper
now we know how much Bobby love songs
big blue ass so that's why I like to put
a blue piece of candy right there just
you show how much Bobby laughs our next
now that Bobby's on we are going to move
over to Sonic now Sonic you much easier
than my obey what you're gonna need to
do is you are just gonna take a big old
dog of that stick oatmeal oh yes
[Music]
I don't need no spoon boom there we go
[ __ ] now what you're going to do is
just since Sonic is like bad and round
and round and [ __ ] you're going to need
to Zeus bones just pile the Mersh into
like a big ball because this is going to
happen in Sonic slack head and [ __ ]
come on socks heads round and what
you're going to need to do is you're
going do next
open it and you here's the fun part
you are going to just dip the knife into
the jelly try not to get too much and
you know how sock has fans we are going
to just draw triangles on the left and
right like this to represent socks fine
see like this one triangle then one two
all that is looking good can't wait to
eat this oh yes look at that
it's oh I looking like saw now he to the
husband father two sides uh-uh
[ __ ] he's got them on both and there
you go third one right there and now if
we just move Bobby over put him with us
cue their lover
no sarcasm but sheets and there you go a
Sonic autumn meal fit for a king
I got taste this [ __ ] wrong that's good
that's a snack on me right mm-hmm
I love this mmm
you see this this is the meal of us of a
true soccer fan you eat wall thing about
soccer around like one more can you are
hmm that what's up I need more honey
more any more meal maybe you want to see
more of those like these meals and [ __ ]
be sure to LIKE comment subscribe let me
know you what let me know what you want
me to make next purchase I'll do it